A Guide to the Papers of Ruth G. Hale 1970-2001
Roanoke Public Libraries
Roanoke Public Libraries
A Guide to the Papers of Ruth G. Hale
Roanoke Public Libraries
2001.1.26
29 letter storage boxes
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Donated by Charles W. Hale, Jr.
Biographical Note
Ruth Gerda Hale was born April 26, 1926 in Bernstadt, Schlesien (Silesia), which then was part of Germany. Her parents were Paul Robert and Meta Gertrud Mcke [sic] Gottschalk. After World War II the family moved to Pocking, West Germany as refugees. Here Ruth met Charles W. Hale, Jr., who was stationed in Pocking with the U.S. Army. They married on February 14, 1948, and Ruth eventually emigrated with her husband to his home in Waiteville in Monroe County, WV. They continued to move frequently, living in West Point, NY, Colorado Springs, CO, Ft. Eustis, Virginia, Japan and Germany before settling in Cloverdale, Botetourt County, VA. Mrs. Hale had three daughters: Irene Joy (Remines), Heidi Marina (Turpin), and Letha Mae Gerda Hale. Genealogy was Mrs. Hale’s passion. She began keeping family records in the mid-1970s, researching her husband’s family connections and the families of whomever asked her for help. Her work focused on Craig County and surrounding areas. In addition to doing local research, she used the Virginia Room of the Roanoke Public Libraries and other libraries and archives. Mrs. Hale was known especially for travelling around to meet with the family members of those she was researching; according to her daughter Heidi, her presence at family reunions in the area soon became both welcome and expected. The materials in this collection clearly show the results of her personal approach. Her work was also a family effort. Mrs. Hale loved hiking, and together she and her husband Charles would go on hikes to record remote cemeteries. Her daughter Heidi also helped, typing the manuscripts for Mrs. Hale’s publications. She published three volumes of Craig County, Virginia marriages (1851-1881, 1882-1910 and 1911-1938) and volumes of the 1920 Census for Craig County and Roanoke County, VA. Ruth Hale lived in Cloverdale at the time of her death, March 25, 2001. She is buried in New Zion Union Church Cemetery, Waiteville, WV.
Scope and Content
This is a genealogical collection focusing on the Hale/Ahl/All families and connecting families. Many other families of Craig County, Virginia and surrounding areas are also included. Materials in the collection include notes, correspondence, news clippings and copies of official records (births, marriages, deaths, cemeteries, funeral homes, military pensions etc.) along with photographs: both originals and copies and photo negatives. Date range for the collection: the collection was created between ca. 1970 and 2001; materials included in the collection cover the 16th-20th centuries, with coverage varying for each family name. Names and locations will turn up multiple times throughout the records. Researchers interested in a certain family or locality should make sure to go through the name files as well as the cemetery files and files organized geographically by county or locality. Geographical designations are made at various levels: county, city or town, and cemetery names. Many of the family records include photographs; there are also photographs of buildings and local historical landmarks. Folders with photographs are marked. This includes original photographs as well as the photocopies Mrs. Hale often made of original family photographs. The cemetery records in the collections often include photographs of markers, maps and Mrs. Hale’s handwritten notes; they may also include obituaries. Mrs. Hale recycled paper. Occasionally a small article of importance will be mounted on a larger piece of which the text is not relevant. Box 25 contains the materials from a box of loose materials including a number of unlabeled antique photographs; it also contains Mrs. Hale’s spiral notebooks. Box 26, the last box in the collection, contains the materials from nine notebooks Mrs. Hale had marked “General.”
Arrangement
Boxes 1-14 are organized by family name, arranged alphabetically; boxes 15-29 contain histories, cemetery and other records arranged loosely by geographical location.
Contents List
- Alls and Anderson Families (Box 1)
  - Alls Family - James Aul, Sr. undated (Folder 1)
  - Alls Family - Josephus All undated (Folder 2)
  - Alls Family - James Alls, Jr. undated (Folder 3)
  - Alls Family - William C. Alls undated (Folder 4)
  - Alls Family - Jacob and Elizabeth Pace undated (Folder 5)
  - Alls Family - Nicholas J. Alls undated (Folder 6)
  - Alls Family - Alls/Hipes undated (Folder 7)
  - Alls Family - Benjamin B. Alls undated (Folder 8)
  - Alls Family - Harvey J. Alls undated (Folder 9)
  - Alls Family - Paris Wade Alls undated (Folder 10)
  - All, Alls, Ahl, Awl Family - Census Records undated (Folder 11)
  - All, Alls, Ahl, Awl Family - Marriages undated (Folder 12)
  - All, Alls, Ahl, Aul, Awl Family - Barton Photographs and Family Reunions undated (Folder 13)
  - All, Alls, Ahl, Aul, Awl Family - Births, Cemeteries, Deaths, Marriages and Photographs undated (Folder 14)
  - Anderson, McNeer, Dillon, Neel Family - Cememteries, Census Records, Correspondence, Deaths undated (Folder 15)
  - Anderson, McNeer, Dillon, Neel Family undated (Folder 16)
  - Anderson Family - Census Records, Marriages and Wills undated (Folder 17)
- All, Anderson, Bean and Allied Families (Box 2)
  - Anderson and All Familes - Bradley undated (Folder 1)
  - Anderson and All Families - Tucker undated (Folder 2)
  - Anderson and All Familes - Nicewander undated (Folder 3)
  - Anderson and All Families - Caldwell and Hogan undated (Folder 4)
  - Anderson and All Familes - Ambrose Myers undated (Folder 5)
  - Anderson and All Families - Kinzer undated (Folder 6)
  - Anderson and All Families - Martin undated (Folder 7)
  - Anderson and All Families - Anderson undated (Folder 8)
  - Anderson and All Families - Gorman and Ratliff undated (Folder 9)
  - Anderson and All Families - George Keffer undated (Folder 10)
  - Anderson and All Families - Wright and Keffer undated (Folder 11)
  - Anderson and All Families - Rock and Doss undated (Folder 12)
  - Anderson and All Families - Drewry undated (Folder 13)
  - Anderson and All Families - Jonathan Givens undated (Folder 14)
  - Anderson and All Families - Lipes and Meyers undated (Folder 15)
  - Anderson and All Families - Myers and Elmore undated (Folder 16)
  - Anderson and All Families - Looney and Dudding undated (Folder 17)
  - Anderson and All Families - Eakin and Bean undated (Folder 18)
  - Ayers Family - History and Reunions undated (Folder 19)
  - Bean Family - James Franklin Bean undated (Folder 20)
  - Bean Family - Sadie Francis Bean undated (Folder 21)
  - Bean Family - Census Records and Marriages undated (Folder 22)
  - Bean Family - Wells and McDonald undated (Folder 23)
  - Bean Family - McDonald undated (Folder 24)
  - Bean Family - Barton undated (Folder 25)
  - Bean Family - Wells undated (Folder 26)
  - Bean Family - Marriages undated (Folder 27)
- Beard, Brand, Bowles, Britts, Huffman and Allied Families (Box 3)
  - Beard and Brand Families - Bean undated (Folder 1)
  - Beard and Brand Families undated (Folder 2)
  - Beard and Brand Families - Hunter undated (Folder 3)
  - Beard and Huffman Families - Lark undated (Folder 4)
  - Beard and Huffman Families - Beard undated (Folder 5)
  - Beard and Huffman Families - Huffman undated (Folder 6)
  - Beard and Huffman Families - Roane County, West Virginia Marriages undated (Folder 7)
  - Beard and Huffman Families - Broce undated (Folder 8)
  - Bennett, McDonald and Shelor Families undated (Folder 9)
  - Book Family - Correspondence undated (Folder 10)
  - Bowles Family undated (Folder 11)
  - Bowles Family - Shaver undated (Folder 12)
  - Bowles Family - Hale undated (Folder 13)
  - Bowles Family undated (Folder 14)
  - Bowles Family - Burkette undated (Folder 15)
  - Bowles Family - Sites undated (Folder 16)
  - Brillhart Family - Census Records and Deaths undated (Folder 17)
  - Britts Family undated (Folder 18)
  - Britts Family - Wright undated (Folder 19)
- Broce, Brookman and Allied Families (Box 4)
  - Broce Family undated (Folder 1-2)
  - Broce Family - Jacob undated (Folder 3)
  - Broce Family - Meadows and Jacob undated (Folder 4)
  - Broce Family - Lawrence County, Ohio undated (Folder 5)
  - Brookman Family undated (Folder 6-7)
- Buck, Caldwell, Camper and Allied Families (Box 5)
  - Buck Family undated (Folder 1-2)
  - Buck Family n- Scanland undated (Folder 3)
  - Buck Family - Census Records undated (Folder 4)
  - Caldwell Family undated (Folder 5)
  - Caldwell Family - Huffman undated (Folder 6)
  - Camper Family undated (Folder 7-8)
  - Camper Family - Cooper and Echols undated (Folder 9)
  - Camper Family - Hurt undated (Folder 10)
- Crowder, Custer, Davis and Allied Families (Box 6)
  - Crowder Family - Huffman and McDonald undated (Folder 1)
  - Custer Family undated (Folder 2)
  - Custer Family - Sirry undated (Folder 3)
  - Custer Family - Brillhart undated (Folder 4)
  - Custer Family - Deeds and Henderson undated (Folder 5)
  - Custer Family - Eakin and Barber undated (Folder 6)
  - Custer Family - Crawford undated (Folder 7)
  - Custer Family - Eakin undated (Folder 8)
  - Custer Family - Grisso undated (Folder 9)
  - Custer Family - Related to all families undated (Folder 10)
  - Dabney, Shrewsberry, Sinkler and Sinclair Families undated (Folder 11)
  - Davis Family - Related to all families undated (Folder 12)
  - Davis Family undated (Folder 13)
  - Davis Family - Cundiff undated (Folder 14)
  - Davis Family - Snead undated (Folder 15)
  - Davis Family - Echols undated (Folder 16)
  - Davis Family - Kirby undated (Folder 17)
- Eckiss, Evans, Furrow, Galloway and Allied Families (Box 7)
  - Eckiss Family undated (Folder 1)
  - Eckiss Family - Shelor undated (Folder 2)
  - Eckiss Family - Broce and Shelor undated (Folder 3)
  - Epling Family - Giles County, Virginia and Monroe County, West Virginia undated (Folder 4)
  - Evans Family undated (Folder 5)
  - Evans Family - Holbrook undated (Folder 6)
  - Evans Family - Litton undated (Folder 7)
  - Evans Family - McReynolds undated (Folder 8)
  - Evans Family - Robinett undated (Folder 9)
  - Ferrell Family undated (Folder 10)
  - Francisco Family undated (Folder 11)
  - Furrow Family undated (Folder 12)
  - Furrow Family - Larch undated (Folder 13)
  - Furrow Family - Craft undated (Folder 14)
  - Furrow Family - Francisco undated (Folder 15)
  - Furrow Family - Morgan undated (Folder 16)
  - Evans Family - Documents for all families undated (Folder 17)
  - Galloway Family undated (Folder 18)
  - Galloway Family - Craig and Walton undated (Folder 19)
  - Galloway Family - Beard and Wright undated (Folder 20)
  - Galloway Family - Stiff undated (Folder 21)
  - Galloway Family - Book undated (Folder 22)
  - Galloway Family - Taylor and Johnson undated (Folder 23)
  - Galloway Family - Graham Kirby undated (Folder 24)
  - Galloway Family - McKenzie undated (Folder 25)
  - Galloway Family - Sink and Kinzer undated (Folder 26)
- Hale, Hall, Harless and Allied Families (Box 8)
  - Hale Family - Hall, Brickey and Ledgerwood undated (Folder 1)
  - Hale Family undated (Folder 2)
  - Hale Family - Brickey, Radford and Porterfield undated (Folder 3)
  - Hall Family - Hale undated (Folder 4)
  - Hall Family - Brickey undated (Folder 5)
  - Hall Family - Wright and Sirry undated (Folder 6)
  - Hall Family - Garman undated (Folder 7)
  - Hall Family - Craft undated (Folder 8)
  - Hall Family - Ledgerwood undated (Folder 9)
  - Hall Family undated (Folder 10)
  - Hall Family - All families undated (Folder 11)
  - Hardwick Family undated (Folder 12)
  - Harless Family undated (Folder 13)
  - Harless Family - Preiss, Price and Grissom undated (Folder 14)
  - Harless Family - Cemetery undated (Folder 15)
  - Obituaries and Anniversaries undated (Folder 16)
- Haymaker, Helton, Hiatt, Hinchee, Huffman, Janelle and Allied Families (Box 9)
  - Haymaker Family - Anderson and Woolwine undated (Folder 1)
  - Helton Family - Hilton, Hylton undated (Folder 2)
  - Hiatt Family - Shockley undated (Folder 3)
  - Hinchee Family - Neel and Duncan undated (Folder 4)
  - Huffman Family - Bush undated (Folder 5)
  - Huffman Family - Carper undated (Folder 6)
  - Huffman Family - Carper, Luster and Bush undated (Folder 7)
  - Huffman Family - Anderson, Simpson and Henderson undated (Folder 8)
  - Huffman Family - Marriages undated (Folder 9)
  - Huffman Family - Greenway, Thomas and Griggs undated (Folder 10)
  - Huffman Family - Photographs and Miscellaneous Documents undated (Folder 11)
  - Huffman Family - Hutchison, Mills and Lafon undated (Folder 12)
  - Hutchinson Family - Miscellaneous Documents undated (Folder 13)
  - Janelle, Jenelle, Journell and Turner Families undated (Folder 14)
- Karr, Keister, Killian, Kinder, Layman, Lee and Allied Families (Box 10)
  - Perdue, Richardson, Martin, Philpott and Ryan Families undated (Folder 1)
  - Karr Family - Harmon, Broce and Linkous undated (Folder 2)
  - Keister Family undated (Folder 3)
  - Killian Family undated (Folder 4)
  - Kinder Family undated (Folder 5)
  - Lafon Family - Correspondence undated (Folder 6)
  - Layman Family - Beard undated (Folder 7)
  - Layman Family undated (Folder 8)
  - Layman Family - Beard undated (Folder 9)
  - Lee Family undated (Folder 10)
- Lee, Lucas, McPherson, Montgomery, Pike and Allied Families (Box 11)
  - Lee Family undated (Folder 1)
  - Lucas Family undated (Folder 2)
  - Lucas Family - Harless undated (Folder 3)
  - Lucas Family - Sarver, Caldwell and Niday undated (Folder 4)
  - Lucas Family undated (Folder 5-7)
  - McPherson Family undated (Folder 8)
  - Montgomery Family undated (Folder 9)
  - Pike Family - Brook undated (Folder 10)
- Pike, Price, Remines, Schlosser and Allied Families (Box 12)
  - Pike Family - Vaughn undated (Folder 1)
  - Pike Family - Bennett undated (Folder 2)
  - Pike Family - Austin and Poole undated (Folder 3)
  - Pike Family - Stoneman undated (Folder 4)
  - Price Family - Preiss and Killman undated (Folder 5)
  - Price Family undated (Folder 6)
  - Price Family - Hoffman undated (Folder 7)
  - Price Family undated (Folder 8)
  - Remines Family - Sawyers, Keys, Slemp, Fry and Testerman undated (Folder 9)
  - Ripley Family - Rockbridge, Botetourt, Craig, Bedford and Monroe Counties undated (Folder 10)
  - Rock Family - Doss, Morgan and Meyers undated (Folder 11)
  - Roller Family undated (Folder 12)
  - Schlosser Family - Slusher and Slusser undated (Folder 13)
- Schlosser, Slusher, Sessler, Skaggs, Smith and Allied Families (Box 13)
  - Schlosser Family - Slusher and Slusser undated (Folder 1)
  - Schlosser Family undated (Folder 2)
  - Slusher Family - Schlosser, Simmons, Rucker and Slusser undated (Folder 3)
  - Skaggs Family undated (Folder 4)
  - Slusher Family - Census Records, Marriages and Deaths undated (Folder 5)
  - Sessler Family undated (Folder 6)
  - Smith Family undated (Folder 7)
  - Smith Family - Census Records undated (Folder 8)
- Smith, Spangler, Sweeney, Turpin, Webb, Wright and Allied Families (Box 14)
  - Smith Family - Wills undated (Folder 1)
  - Smith Family undated (Folder 2)
  - Spangler Family - Young undated (Folder 3)
  - Sweeney Family - All, Hall, Jewell, Holloway, and Songer - Births, Deaths, Marriages and Photographs undated (Folder 4)
  - Turpin Family undated (Folder 5)
  - Webb Family undated (Folder 6)
  - Wright Family - William Greenbury Family Bible undated (Folder 7)
  - Wright Family - "The Wright People" undated (Folder 8)
- Cemetery Records (Box 15)
  - Bath County - Mount Hope Presbyterian Church undated (Folder 1)
  - Franklin County - Boones Mill Baptist Church undated (Folder 2)
  - Franklin County - Dillon Family Cemetery undated (Folder 3)
  - Franklin County - Pate Family Cemetery undated (Folder 4)
  - Franklin County - Shaver Family Cemetery undated (Folder 5)
  - Franklin County - Webb Family Cemetery undated (Folder 6)
  - Giles County - Clover Hollow Cemetery undated (Folder 7)
  - Rockbridge County - Shafer Family Cemetery undated (Folder 8)
  - Obituaries undated (Folder 9)
  - Bedford County undated (Folder 10)
  - Bedford County - Bowling Family Cemetery undated (Folder 11)
  - Bedford County - Union United Methodist Church, McMannaway Family and Bowyer Family Cemeteries undated (Folder 12)
  - Bedford County - Bowles, Leftwich and Clingenpeel Family Cemeteries undated (Folder 13)
  - Bedford County - Nazareth Church and Coffee Family Cemeteries undated (Folder 14)
  - Bedford County - Cool Springs Presbyterian Church undated (Folder 15)
  - Bedford County - Cundiff Family Cemetery undated (Folder 16)
  - Bedford County - Davis Family Cemetery undated (Folder 17)
  - Bedford County - Haynes Family Cemetery undated (Folder 18)
  - Bedford County - Jeter Chapel undated (Folder 19)
  - Bedford County - Mount Zion Baptist Church and Murray Family Cememteries undated (Folder 20)
  - Bedford County - Oakland United Methodist Church undated (Folder 21)
  - Bedford County - Peaks Community Cemetery undated (Folder 22)
  - Bedford County - Bedford Presbyterian and Montvale Baptist Church Cemeteries undated (Folder 23)
  - Bedford County - Stiff Family Cemetery undated (Folder 24)
  - Bedford County - Walnut Grove Church undated (Folder 25)
  - Bedford County - Wright Family Cemetery undated (Folder 26)
  - Bedford County - Old Ebenezer Church undated (Folder 27)
  - Bedford County - Huddleston Cemetery undated (Folder 28)
  - Bedford County - Longwood and Oakwood Cemeteries undated (Folder 29)
  - Bedford County - Watson Family Cemetery undated (Folder 30)
  - Bedford County - Lithia Baptist Church undated (Folder 31)
  - Bedford County - Burkholder Family Cemetery undated (Folder 32)
  - Bedford County - Flowers Family Cemetery undated (Folder 33)
  - Bedford County - Shady Grove Baptist Church undated (Folder 34)
  - Bedford County - St. Thomas Episcopal Church undated (Folder 35)
  - Botetourt County - Anderson Family Cemetery undated (Folder 36)
  - Botetourt County - Bryant Family Cemetery undated (Folder 37)
  - Botetourt County - Copps Family Cemetery undated (Folder 38)
  - Botetourt County - Crawford Family Cemetery undated (Folder 39)
  - Botetourt County - Forest Chapel undated (Folder 40)
  - Botetourt County - Forest Grove Baptist Church undated (Folder 41)
  - Botetourt County - Glade Creek undated (Folder 42)
  - Botetourt County - Old Glade Creek undated (Folder 43)
  - Botetourt County - John Greybill Cemetery undated (Folder 44)
  - Botetourt County - Haymakertown, Sessler and Watkins Family Cemeteries undated (Folder 45)
  - Botetourt County - Laymantown Cemetery undated (Folder 46)
  - Botetourt County - Lemon Family Cemetery undated (Folder 47)
  - Botetourt County - Longdale Cemetery undated (Folder 48)
  - Botetourt County - McKalister Family Cemetery undated (Folder 49)
  - Botetourt County - Mount Bethel Church of the Brethren undated (Folder 50)
  - Botetourt County - Mount Moriah Church undated (Folder 51)
  - Botetourt County - Mount Pleasant United Methodist and White Church Cemeteries undated (Folder 52)
  - Botetourt County - Owen Family Cemetery undated (Folder 53)
  - Botetourt County - Patterson Family Cemetery undated (Folder 54)
  - Botetourt County - Piney Grove undated (Folder 55)
  - Botetourt County - Riley Family Cemetery undated (Folder 56)
  - Botetourt County - Roaring Run and Mt. Olivet Cemeteries undated (Folder 57)
  - Botetourt County - Spangler Family Cemetery undated (Folder 58)
  - Botetourt County - St. Jacobs Church undated (Folder 59)
  - Botetourt County - Tucker Family Cemetery undated (Folder 60)
  - Botetourt County - Watson Family Cemetery undated (Folder 61)
  - Botetourt County - Wheatland Lutheran Church undated (Folder 62)
  - Botetourt County - Williamson-Matheny Family Cemetery undated (Folder 63)
  - Botetourt County - Zion Hill Baptist Church undated (Folder 64)
- Cemetery Records (Box 16)
  - Botetourt County undated (Folder 1)
  - Botetourt County - Cloverdale Cemetery undated (Folder 2)
  - Botetourt County - Forest Chapel undated (Folder 3)
  - Botetourt County - Riley Family Cemetery undated (Folder 4)
  - Botetourt County - Firebaugh Family Cemetery undated (Folder 5)
  - Botetourt County - John Graybill Cemetery undated (Folder 6)
  - Botetourt County - Wheatland undated (Folder 7)
  - Botetourt County - Roaring Run and Mt. Olivet Cemeteries undated (Folder 8)
  - Botetourt County - Robinson Family and Solitude Cemeteries undated (Folder 9)
  - Botetourt County - Watson Family Cemetery undated (Folder 10)
  - Botetourt County - Presbyterian Graveyard undated (Folder 11)
  - Botetourt County - Simmons Family Cemetery undated (Folder 12)
  - Botetourt County - Anderson Family Cemetery undated (Folder 13)
  - Botetourt County - Crawford Family Cemetery undated (Folder 14)
  - Botetourt County - King Family Cemetery undated (Folder 15)
  - Botetourt County - McKalister Family Cemetery undated (Folder 16)
  - Botetourt County - Tucker Family Cemetery undated (Folder 17)
  - Botetourt County - Lemon Family Cemetery undated (Folder 18)
  - Botetourt County - Oriskany undated (Folder 19)
  - Botetourt County - Noftsinger, Styne and Pico Family Cemeteries undated (Folder 20)
  - Botetourt County - Bethel undated (Folder 21)
  - Botetourt County - Blue Ridge Church of the Brethren undated (Folder 22)
  - Botetourt County - Old Glade Creek undated (Folder 23)
  - Botetourt County - Glade Creek undated (Folder 24)
  - Botetourt County - Emmanuel Episcopal Church undated (Folder 25)
  - Botetourt County - Forest Grove undated (Folder 26)
  - Botetourt County - Longdale undated (Folder 27)
  - Botetourt County - Mt. Bethel Church of the Brethren undated (Folder 28)
  - Botetourt County - Mt. Moriah Church undated (Folder 29)
  - Botetourt County - Mt. Pleasant and White Church Cemeteries undated (Folder 30)
  - Botetourt County - Owen Family Cemetery undated (Folder 31)
  - Botetourt County - New Hope undated (Folder 32)
  - Botetourt County - Piney Grove undated (Folder 33)
  - Botetourt County - Rudisill Family Cemetery undated (Folder 34)
  - Botetourt County - St. Jacobs Church undated (Folder 35)
  - Botetourt County - Wesley Chapel undated (Folder 36)
  - Botetourt County - Zion Hill Baptist Church undated (Folder 37)
  - Botetourt County - Unnamed Cemetery near Hunt Club undated (Folder 38)
  - Botetourt County - Andrew Chapel undated (Folder 39)
  - Botetourt County - Copps Family Cemetery undated (Folder 40)
  - Botetourt County - Williamson-Matheny Family Cemetery undated (Folder 41)
  - Botetourt County - Spangler Family Cemetery undated (Folder 42)
  - Botetourt County - Springwood Baptist Church undated (Folder 43)
  - Botetourt County - Haymakertown, Sessler and Watkins Family Cemeteries undated (Folder 44)
  - Botetourt County - Shiloh undated (Folder 45)
  - Botetourt County - A History of... undated (Folder 46)
- Craig County Records and Families (Box 17)
  - Schools - Catawba Valley undated (Folder 1)
  - Funeral Home Records - Boitnott-Reynolds. undated (Folder 2)
  - Schools undated (Folder 3)
  - Robert Craig undated (Folder 4)
  - Houses undated (Folder 5)
  - World War I - News clippings from New Castle undated (Folder 6)
  - Meadows Family undated (Folder 7)
  - Brugh Family undated (Folder 8)
  - Woods Family undated (Folder 9)
  - Crowder Family Cemetery undated (Folder 10)
  - Yoder-Walker and Wagener-Caldwell Family Cemeteries undated (Folder 11)
  - Carper Family Cemetery undated (Folder 12)
  - Ruble Family Cemetery undated (Folder 13)
  - Waugh Family Cemetery undated (Folder 14)
  - West View Cemetery undated (Folder 15)